{
  "LevelId": 23,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 230,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BUTTERFLY",
      "question": "Colorful insect with wings"
    },
    {
      "id": 231,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BACKYARDS",
      "question": "Outdoor spaces behind houses"
    },
    {
      "id": 232,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "AUTHORESS",
      "question": "Female author"
    },
    {
      "id": 233,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "TECHNIQUE",
      "question": "Methods and skills"
    },
    {
      "id": 234,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BARBEQUED",
      "question": "popular method of cooking meat outdoors, often involving grilling or smoking"
    },
    {
      "id": 235,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "AIRSPEEDS",
      "question": "describe the speed of an aircraft relative to the air in which it is flying"
    },
    {
      "id": 236,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "AMBULANCE",
      "question": "vehicle is equipped to transport individuals in need of urgent medical care to a healthcare facility"
    },
    {
      "id": 237,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "CONCOCTED",
      "question": "describes the process of creating or preparing something, typically a mixture or recipe"
    },
    {
      "id": 238,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "DISTROYED",
      "question": "opposite of \"built\" or \"constructed\""
    },
    {
      "id": 239,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "FREQUENCY",
      "question": "often does something occur or repeat"
    }
  ]
}